https://eshowcase.com/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy
This is the Privacy Policy of ESHOWCASE, INC.
1. Introduction1.1 We value and are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.1.2 Accordingly, this Privacy Policy (together with our Terms of Website Use and any other documents referred to in it) governs the way in which we process, use and store any personal information that you provide us and/or we collect from you.1.3 Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and in conjunction with our Terms of Website Use of which it forms part.1.4 www.internetmarketingtrainingclub.com is owned and operated by ESHOWCASE, INC.1.5 For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 198, the data controller is ESHOWCASE, INC., whose registered office is at 10785 W. Twain Ave. Ste 102. Las Vegas, NV, 89135, United States.1.6 If you have any queries about this site or our Privacy Policy, please contact us viawriting to us at the above address or by Phone: +1 (702) 919-61462. What Information is Collected2.1 IP Addresses and Cookies2.1.1 A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user.2.1.2When you visit our website, it will send your computer a session cookie containing a unique and anonymous identifier.2.1.3 The website server will create a corresponding but anonymous record of a number of technical details including your IP address, details of your operating system and the date, time and duration of your visit to our website.2.1.4 Once your visit to our website had ended, the cookie will be automatically deleted.2.1.5 We use cookies site to track the pages and articles visited. We use this information to see which items are (or are not) of greatest interest to visitors.2.1.6 If you want to stop cookies being stored on your computer in future, please refer to your browser manufacturer’s instructions by clicking ‘Help’ in your browser menu.2.1.7 If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.2.1.8 Further information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.AboutCookies.org2.2 Personal Data2.2.1 Personal information you may submit to us may include• Information that you provide by filling in forms on www.internetmarketingtrainingclub.com (our website).• This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our website, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We collect information you volunteer when you answer a survey; enter a competition or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our site. If you contact us we may keep a record of that correspondence.• Details of transactions you carry out through our website and of the fulfilment of your orders.• Details of your visits to our website (including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and other communication data, whether this is required for own billing purposes or otherwise) and the resources that you access.3. How We May Use Your Information3.1 We may use your information, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods or services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by email or post.3.2 We will use your information for the purpose of providing the services you have requested, processing any other transactions authorised or made by you with us, informing you of our events and other marketing information to you which we think you may find of interest and undertaking product or client research.3.3 If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data we (or they) will contact you by electronic means or post only if you have consented to this.3.4 If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please send as an email marked unsubscribe on the form on which we collect your data.3.5 If you are an existing customer we will only contact you by electronic means or post with information about goods and services similar to those which are the subject of a previous sale to you.3.6 We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users. We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target.3.7 We use the information to improve our services.3.8 The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website, and is never shared for commercial purposes.3.9 We will process your information as mentioned above will do so in accordance with this Privacy Policy.3.10 Apart from the uses described in the paragraphs above the only circumstances in which we could disclose any of this information to any third party are: if ownership of all or part of our website were transferred, in which case any purchaser would only be entitled to use that information in a way consistent with this Privacy Policy; or if we are required to do so by any regulatory or criminal authority.4. Where This Information Is Stored4.1 The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”).4.2 It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us, or for one of our suppliers.4.3 Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services.4.4 By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.5. Security5.1 Our Security Policy outlines all security measures we enforce to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.5.2 However, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you disclose to us.5.3 You accept the inherent risks of providing information and dealing on-line and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security.5.4 Please read our Security Policy on what measures we enforce.6. Links6.1 Our site may, from time to time contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.6.2 If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.6.3 Please read our Terms of Website Use for further information on these links.6.4 We strongly recommend that you read the privacy policy of any such websites that you visit.7. CHANGES7.1 We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time to reflect any changes to our privacy practices in accordance with changes to legislation, best practice or website enhancements.7.2 We will let you now what these changes are by posting them on this page, but it is your responsibility as a user to make sure that you are aware of them, by checking for any changes on a regular basis.7.3 Changes will become effective as soon as they are posted.7.4 You should therefore review this page regularly to ensure that you are aware of any change to its terms.
Please Enquire For Further Information About Any Of Our Products & Services
eShowcase Inc..
10785 W. Twain Ave. Ste. 102, Las Vegas, NV 89135
+1 (702) 919-6146
support@eshowcase.net
www.eShowcase.net
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Subject
Your Message
Privacy Policy | Terms of services | Cookie Policy | Intellectual Property Notice | FTC Disclaimer | Earnings Disclaimer
Copyright © 2019 eShowcase Inc. All rights reserved.
